<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recipes on</title><link>https://appservR.github.io/docs/recipes/</link><description>Recent content in Recipes on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://appservR.github.io/docs/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Customize styling</title><link>https://appservR.github.io/docs/recipes/customize-styling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://appservR.github.io/docs/recipes/customize-styling/</guid><description>Customize html templates # All buit-in pages, such as signup, login, error pages, are embeded in AppservR executable. However, they can be changed easily if you want to translate them to your language, add your company&amp;rsquo;s logo, etc.
You just need to create a templates directory at the same location as the executable file. AppservR will look for existing files in this directory before falling back to the default templates.</description></item><item><title>Manage user authentication</title><link>https://appservR.github.io/docs/recipes/manage-auth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://appservR.github.io/docs/recipes/manage-auth/</guid><description>Manage users # You can create new users via the admin interface, or users can sign up themselves.
Users belong to groups that you can create through the admin interface. By default, the first user to sign up belongs to the admins group. The admins group cannot be renamed nor removed, and admin users cannot remove themselves from this group.
Access control # You can control who is allowed to access each app:</description></item><item><title>Install as a service</title><link>https://appservR.github.io/docs/recipes/install-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://appservR.github.io/docs/recipes/install-service/</guid><description>Manage service via the CLI # The appservr service command allows installing and managing the AppservR service on Windows an Linux.
💡 Managing services requires to run a command prompt as admin on Windows. Install # appservr service install sub-command installs AppservR as a service (running the executable file at its current location).
On Windows, only admins can install services, and services run with administrative privileges by default.</description></item></channel></rss>